W. R. "Bob" Poage Texas Development papers, Inclusive: 1913-1979, undated, Bulk: 1946-1978
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Water Resources, 1913-1978, undated; 2
  - U.S. Supreme Court, Motion for Bill of Particulars, U.S.A. v. State of Texas, 1948 October (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Supreme Court, Supplemental Statement, U.S.A. v. State of Texas, 1948 October (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Supreme Court, Amended Motion for Order, U.S.A. v. State of Texas, 1949 October (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - U.S. Supreme Court, Answer of the State of Texas, U.S.A. v. State of Texas, 1949 October (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Supreme Court, Appointment of a Special Master, U.S.A. v. State of Texas, 1949 October (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - U.S. Supreme Court, Brief, U.S.A. v. State of Texas, 1949 October (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - U.S. Supreme Court, Brief for the State of Texas in Opposition to Motion for Judgment, U.S.A. v. State of Texas, 1949 October (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Supreme Court, Defendant’s Petition for Rehearing, U.S.A. v. State of Texas, 1949 October (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Supreme Court, First Amended Answer of the State of Texas, U.S.A. v. State of Texas, 1949 October (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Supreme Court, Motion for Order to Take Oral Depositions, U.S.A. v. State of Texas, 1949 October (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Supreme Court, Reply in Opposition to Motion for Judgment, U.S.A. v. State of Texas, 1949 October (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Supreme Court, Reply Memorandum, U.S.A. v. State of Texas, 1949 October (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Supreme Court, Brief of Amicus Curiae, U.S.A. v. State of Texas, circa 1950 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Supreme Court, Oral Argument, U.S.A. v. State of Texas, 1950 March 28 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Supreme Court, Defendant’s Petition for Rehearing Directed to the Court’s Amended Opinion”, U.S.A. v. State of Texas, 1950 October (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - U.S. Supreme Court, Objection to the Decree Proposed by the United States, U.S.A. v. State of Texas, 1950 October (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - University of Texas College of Engineering, Center for Research in Water Resources, Annual Report, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Waco Chamber of Commerce, Packet, “Flood Control and Water Supply Needs, Waco, Texas”, 1954 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Water Policy Committee of National Reclamation Association, Report, “A National Water Policy”, 1952 (Box 31, Folder 13)